Hi!
In this series of clips, I'm going to show you how to organize your various scrapbook supplies.
Decorative scissors are really fun to use when scrapbooking and they really add a great extra flare to any page.
The problem is what to do with all those scissors that you accumulate.
If you have a bunch of scrapbook scissors that you bought separately, probably one of the best ways to organize those is just to buy a plastic container like this and put all of your scissors in there.
That way you can just dump them all in there and dig through them as you need them.
If you don't have that many, you can always just use a drawer tray like this, which is really nice because you can just slide it in a drawer and out of sight out of mind when you're not scrapbooking.
If you buy all of your scissors together, a lot of times they'll come in an organizer all ready.
This one's really nice because it spins and you can see all of the different cuts that it makes already on the scissors.
If you haven't bought scissors for your scrapbook station yet, to go ahead and buy all of them together at once already in an organizing system.
You also want to make sure that along with all your decorative scissors, you have just a regular pair of scissors for any other cutting you might want to do.
A lot of scrapbookers will have a cutting system where you have different utensils that you use to cut different shapes.
The easiest way to organize these is just to find a small container where you can stack all these and your little cutting blades.